export const objectData = [{
    question: "who is Alfredo",
    choice: [" person ", " aircraft ", " bird ", " plant "],
    answer: "a person"
}, {
    question: "Where is he coming from",
    choice: ["venezuela ", 'uruguay ', 'brasil ', 'argentina '],
    answer: "venezuela"
}, {
    question: "how old is he",
    choice: ["34 ", '55 ', '85 ', '20'],
    answer: "35"
}, {
    question: "what is his favorite number",
    choice: ["7 ", '55 ', '85 ', '20'],
    answer: "7"
}, {
    question: "what is his favorite food",
    choice: ["pizza ", '55 ', '85 ', '20'],
    answer: "pizza"
}, {
    question: "how many sibbling does he have",
    choice: ["3 ", '55 ', '85 ', '20'],
    answer: "3"
}, {
    question: "what cellphone does he have",
    choice: ["iphone ", '55 ', '85 ', '20'],
    answer: "iphone"
}, {
    question: "what is his biggest degree achieved",
    choice: ["bachelor ", '55 ', '85 ', '20'],
    answer: "bachelor"
}, {
    question: "what is the name is his middle school",
    choice: ["carlota ", '55 ', '85 ', '20'],
    answer: "carlota"
}, {
    question: "where did he study",
    choice: ["san cristobal ", '55 ', '85 ', '20'],
    answer: "san cristobal"
}, {
    question: "where had not he worked",
    choice: ["saturn ", '55 ', '85 ', '20'],
    answer: "saturn"
}, {
    question: "how tall is he",
    choice: ["8 inches ", '55 ', '85 ', '20'],
    answer: "8 inches"
}, {
    question: "what are his hobbies",
    choice: ["domino ", '55 ', '85 ', '20'],
    answer: "domino"
}, {
    question: "what is his civil state",
    choice: ["married ", '55 ', '85 ', '20'],
    answer: "married"
}]

